freewarefiles.com 2002-06-01

# Freeware Files.com - Privacy Policy

**Freeware Files.com Privacy Policy**

* * *

FreewareFiles.com is aware of the importance in protecting the privacy of information provided by its users. Information is never collected from our visitors without their prior knowledge and consent. This Privacy Policy summarizes how we handle that information. 

**Information Freeware Files.com Collects**

FreewareFiles.com collects information about its users during their registration for our newsletters, software submissions, contests, and polls. Information provided to us is used for internal purposes and for periodic opt-in newsletters to which users have subscribed. Information is never collected without the users knowledge. FreewareFiles.com will not reveal information provided by its users to any third party without their permission.

Personally Identifiable information collected by FreewareFiles.com may include, but is not limited to: First Name, Last Name, E-mail Address, Postal Code, Country, Gender, and Occupation. For developers who submit their software to our site, FreewareFiles.com only collects the software author's email address for internal purposes only. Software developers will occasionally receive email regarding their program listings and information regarding site updates which may directly effect the software developer's listing.

**How We Use Your Information**

FreewareFiles.com uses the information that we collect from you to process your requests and to inform you of our new service offerings and website updates. Users will not receive e-mail from other companies or individuals unless users have requested to be placed on a list to receive information from our advertisers and/or marketing partners on subjects of interest. Users have the option to "opt-out" of our newsletters and may request to have their provided information removed from our database. Users also have the option to "opt-out" from receiving requested information provided by our advertisers and/or marketing partners.

Please be aware that when you click on any advertising banners appearing on our web site that take you to third-party web sites, you will be subject to the their privacy policies and not ours. While we support the protection of privacy on our site, we cannot be responsible for the actions of third parties. We encourage you to read the posted privacy statement prior to providing any personal information to and/or interacting with any other web site.

Software developers who hold individual accounts with FreewareFiles.com for the purpose of publishing their software product on our site should be aware that all information provided to us regarding your software products will be used soley at our discretion. FreewareFiles.com maintains the right to add product information, edit product information, or completely remove product information at any time without the consent of the software developer. FreewareFiles.com may also evaluate the product and express its evaluation publicly on our web site. Additionally, visitors to our web site may also rate and review the software developer's product and have that information published on our web site without prior consent from the software developer.

**How to Access, Correct, or Remove Your Information**

Individual account holders with FreewareFiles.com may, at any time, access their product information through the use of their private accounts. Users may add, delete, or modify their product information without prior permission from FreewareFiles.com, but before information is published on our site, all product information will be reviewed and must be approved by us. To protect your privacy and security, we take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. Only you can access this account by using your unique Logon ID and Password.

You may request deletion of your FreewareFiles.com account by contacting Customer Support at: [**support@freewarefiles.com**](mailto:support@freewarefiles.com)

Individuals who are subscribers to our newsletter or requested to receive information from our marketing partners who wish to remove their Demographic or Personally Identifiable information collected by us, may do so by contacting: [**lists@freewarefiles.com**](mailto:lists@freewarefiles.com)

**Third Party Privacy**

Freeware Files.com works with a third-party that serves ads to this site. In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertisers may place or recognize unique "cookies" on your browser and may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this and other web sites about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, following are the third-party advertisers which currently serve ads to this site. 

Please visit these providers individually to learn more about how they handle your privacy. 

WebTrends Live is used to analyze traffic to this web site. WebTrends Live does not create individual profiles for visitors. Unlike some tracking services WebTrends Live does not have a database of individual profiles for each visitor. WebTrends Live only collects aggregate data. For more information about WebTrends Live privacy policy, please [**click here**](http://www.webtrendslive.com/privacy_policy.htm).

**How to Contact Us**

Should you have any questions or concerns about this privacy policy , please contact: [**privacy@freewarefiles.com**](mailto:privacy@freewarefiles.com)
